[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the sin that murderer John Doe saves for last in the 1995 movie Seven?", "correct_answer": "Wrath", "incorrect_answers": ["Gluttony", "Envy", "Sloth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which 2002 movie is this audio clip from?", "correct_answer": "My Big Fat Greek Wedding", "incorrect_answers": ["Eat Drink Man Woman", "The Wedding Banquet", "Betsys Wedding"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Star Wars Princess Leia is being held at what block on the Death Star?", "correct_answer": "1138", "incorrect_answers": ["1553", "1838", "1332"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Were the shells of all ammonites coiled?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1979 movie sequel, written and directed by Sylvester Stallone, grossed $200,000,000 USD.", "correct_answer": "Rocky II", "incorrect_answers": ["The Exorcist III", "The Godfather III", "Beverly Hills Cop II"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Was the Pascaline invented by Blaise Pascal?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these animals does dipterology study?", "correct_answer": "Flies", "incorrect_answers": ["Moles", "Foxes", "Lizards"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pigeons are master nest builders.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Steven Spielbergs movie, The Color Purple,  was nominated for 11 Academy Awards, how many did it actually win?", "correct_answer": "0", "incorrect_answers": ["5", "3", "8"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "John Adams was the second President of the United States. Who was the second Vice-President of the United States?", "correct_answer": "Thomas Jefferson", "incorrect_answers": ["John Hancock", "John Quincy Adams", "Ben Franklin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Dodgeball, Coach Patches OHoulihan was a big believer in the five Ds of dodgeball which were dodge, duck, dip, dive and _____________.", "correct_answer": "dodge", "incorrect_answers": ["dink", "deliver", "dunk"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Dirty Dancing, which of the following did Baby not perform during her first dance at Sheldrake?", "correct_answer": "The Lift", "incorrect_answers": ["Johnnys arm sliding down her body (because she laughs)", "The bow at the end", "Some of the steps"]}]